剧情回顾...
Previously on lost...
救命!
help me!
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
他是他们的一员
He is one of them.
她很好  她会没事的
She's okay. She's gonna be all right.
-你在哪儿找到她的?  -在她菜园边上
-Where did you find her?  -Just outside our garden.
快上床吧
马上来了
你看起来很美
噢  真是的
转个身吧
亲爱的...
来吧...
你量过体温了吗?
真不浪漫
对不起
只是...已经一年了
我想我们还是去看下医生吧
看医生?
产科医生
你为什么这么在意那个  你也许见都见不到的孩子?
不要指责我的工作  Sun 我努力干我们才...
工作?
当你满手是血的回家  这不叫工作
那你想想我为什么满手是血的回家?
都是因为你父亲  是他让我做的
我不是故意的...我很抱歉
也许等我们有了孩子后...
你父亲会改变他的主意
我们给他生个孙子
他也许会给我个安全点的活干
孩子可以改变一切
会让生活变得更好
Jin...吓了我一跳
你知道我找了你多久么? 你在这儿干什么?
你说什么啊?  我在菜园里干活啊
来吧  我们回去
什么?  不要
走吧  我们现在就回去
你还想再被劫么?
什么?
你在这儿被其他人袭击过
我们说过这事了  跟我走
我不需要你保护我
我只是在我的菜园里干活
什么?  我的菜园?
停下  拜托  住手
现在你没理由来这儿了吧
可以回去了么?
跑得这么快  后面有鬼追你么?
You were running like the devil's chasing you.
也许是吧
Maybe he is.
对你保持身材有好处
Good for you, keeping in shape.
你想要干吗  Locke?
What do you want, Locke?
我要干吗?
What do I want?
我在这儿一个多星期了
I've been here over a week.
你从没和我说过什么话
You've never said two words to me,
现在你却坐在我帐篷外面
and now you're sitting outside my tent?
舱子里关着一个人
We got a man locked up down in the hatch.
有可能是他们中的一个...其他人
There's a possibility he's one of them...the others.
他现在在看着他
He's keeping watch right now.
-我们是谁?  -我和Jack
-Who's we?  -Me and Jack.
他被关多久了?
How long has he been down there?
三天
Three days.
我想让你和他谈谈
I'd like you to talk with him.
你有和其他人接触过的经验  你曾经是个警察
You have experience with the others. You were a cop.
对我来说你是最好的人选  去辨别一下
Seems to me you're the most qualified to figure out
这个人说的是否是真话
if this man's telling the truth.
Jack知道你为这事来找我么?
Does jack know you're coming to me with this?
我们大家有个大问题  Ana Lucia...我们大家
We got a serious problem, Ana Lucia...all of us.
我只是为了能解决它
I'm taking the necessary steps to solve it.
和你谈话我不需要Jack的允许 因为现在
I don't need Jack's permission to talk with you, because right now,
在舱里有个人  我想放他出来
there's a man sitting in a room in my hatch, and I want him out.
我不需要你给什么
I don't wanna give you anything.
只要想想就好了  但你没去想
It's the thought that counts,and you just didn't think.
我整天在想
I think all the time.
也许你该让我在这儿歇一会儿
Maybe you should think about giving me a little bit of a break here.
别说了  Bernard  别说了
Oh,  just hush, Bernard. Just hush.
亲爱的?  你没事吧?
Honey? Are you all right?
我...我想我只是有点头晕
I'm... I think I'm just a little lightheaded.
你脸色像纸一样苍白
Well, you look as pale as a sheet.
快给她点水喝
Well, give her some water.
好的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
别理他  亲爱的  他疯了
Don't pay him any mind, honey.
他居然忘了我的生日
He's just mad at the world because he forgot my birthday.
我没忘  我只是不知道 今天到底是星期几  Rose
I didn't forget. I don't even know what day of the week it is, Rose.
星期六  Bernard
It's saturday,Bernard.
亲爱的  你还能走么?
Can you walk, honey?
可以  我还好
Really, I'm all right.
-也许我们得叫Jin来  -不
-Maybe  we should go get jin.  -No!
我想我只是太阳晒多了
I think I was just out in the sun too long.
你整天和孩子呆在一起
Well, you spend a lot of time around the baby.
也许得了什么病  至少问问Jack
Maybe you caught something. At least talk to Jack.
真的不用了  我很好 谢谢你们两个
Really,I'm okay. Thank you, both of you.
路上很堵么?
和往常一样
他知道你在这吗?
不知道
我以为你会告诉他
不可能的
你今天能抽空过来我很高兴
这是作为经理和酒店老板 的独子的难得空闲啊
可自由支配的时间
房间也不是太旧
要喝点什么吗?
请来杯冰茶吧
用英语怎么说?
In english?
我...我想要杯冰茶
I'll...hmm...I would like an iced tea. Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吧?
我很好
要谈谈那件事么?
不用了
如果你改变主意的话...
可以不用接受我的建议
不过你会说英文Jin一定会很高兴的
但他问起我是怎么学  向谁学时 我该怎么说呢
如果你觉得我们这样会面有问题 就不用继续下去了
-这是你希望的么?  -不是
我也能练练英语
早上好
Jack Morning, Jack.
你就不能等我洗完再进来么?
You couldn't wait until I was done in here?
蒸汽使我毛孔扩张
The steam opens up my pores.
我们没有剃须沫  得随时等机会
Man's got no shaving cream, he's got to improvise.
我想现在就是个好时候了
I also thought this might be a good time
来谈谈我们的问题
to talk about our problem.
我们的问题
Our problem.
Henry的问题  我们已经关了他三天了
Our Henry problem. We've had him locked up for three days now,
我爱莫能助  只是觉得我们
and I can't help but get the sense that he's just not
无法让他和我们合作
motivated to cooperate with us.
那我们可以有什么办法呢  John
John? And how are we gonna motivate him,John?
我想我们是没办法了
I don't think there's anything we can do.
我们得试试别人
I think we need to bring in some new blood.
很明显你有人选了
Obviously you have someone in mind.
你看Ana Lucia怎么样?
What do you think about Ana Lucia?
为什么是她?
Why her?
你要建军队和那些人战斗时  她是你找的人
She's the one you went to to start an army to fight these people.
那为什么不是她?
Why not her?
除非你担心她会对他做什么
Unless you're worried about what she'll do to him.
我去和她谈谈
I'll talk to her.
我谈过了
I already did.
她已经在房间里了
She's in there with him now.
你也是飞机上的么?
Were you on the plane,too?
我在尾部
I was in the tail section.
我们坠落在岛的另一边
We crashed on the other side of the island.
你是穿过整个岛过来的?
You walked across? All the way here?
一定很有趣吧
That must have been fun.
有时是的
It had its moments.
那么你来讲讲你的故事吧  Henry
Henry So are you gonna tell me your story, Henry?
Jack  Locke为什么烦恼?  我已经和所有人说过了
Jack  Locke Why bother? I've already told it to everyone
Jack  Locke  那个在我面前割胡须的黑大个
Jack, Locke, the big black guy that cut off his beard in front of me.
噢  还有我的伙伴Sayid
Oh, yeah, and my buddy Sayid.
看看我的脸就知道他有多喜欢我的故事了
You can see how much he liked my story.
那么为什么不和我说说?
So how about you try me?
我不是不领情  但是...
I don't mean to be ungrateful, but...
你为什么要帮我离开这儿?
why are you gonna help me get out of here?
在岛的另一边
On the other side of the island,
有这么个人和我们一起
there was this guy with us.
我百分百肯定他不是飞机上的
I was 100% convinced that he wasn't on the plane.
所以我挖了个洞  把他扔了进去
So I dug a hole, and I threw him in it.
然后呢?
And what happened?
是我错了  现在他死了
I was wrong. And now he's dead.
但是有个好消息  Henry 我不会两次犯同样的错误
But good news for you, Henry...I don't make the same mistake twice.
所以你最好和我说说你的故事
So how about you tell me your story?
Sawyer?
噢  好啊  有事么?
Well, hey there, sunshine. What can I do for you?
这本书怎样?
How's your book?
情节猜都猜得到 性描写也不多
Predictable.Not nearly enough sex.
我听说药物供给都在你那儿
I heard that you have all the, uh, medical supplies.
是的
You heard correct.
我能看看有什么吗?
May I look through them?
不可以
No,
但是如果你告诉我你要找什么...
you may not. But if you'll tell me what you're lookin' for...
算了
Forget it.
好了  等等
Okay, hold on.
现在我很感兴趣
Now I'm intrigued.
告诉你...
Tell you what...
我和你说  告诉我你想找什么 我就白送给你
tell me what you're lookin' for, and it's yours. Gratis.
我就不能自己找么?
Can't I just look myself?
亲爱的  这可不是在药房里
It's not a drugstore, sweetheart.
我要...一根测孕棒
I need...a pregnancy test.
我什么都听不到
I can't hear anything.
她才进去了三十分钟
She's only been in there about 30 minutes.
你怎么知道他没有扭Ana的脖子  John?
How do you know he hasn't snapped her neck, John?
那你怎么知道Ana没有扭他的脖子?
How do you know she hasn't snapped his?
那么我就直说了
So let me get this straight
你们夫妻乘一个有笑脸的热气球环球旅行坠毁在这
you and your wife travel around the world and crash here in a smiley face balloon.
然后她死了
Then she dies.
你被一个法国人抓了  并被她带来这里
You get captured by a french chick who brings you here,
你这么说听起来有点傻  然后他们把你关了起来
Sounds kind of silly when you say it like that. and then they lock you up.
你为什么没胡须?
Why don't you have a beard?
因为我刮过
Because I shaved.
这些平常人做的事情我也需要
Because I needed something normal.
好的
Okay.
那么你为什么不画一张去热气球那儿的地图呢?
So why don't you draw me a map to your balloon?
我们去那儿找到的话
We'll go out there. We'll find it,
大家就会相信你了
and everybody will believe you.
他们一直要我画...画一张地图
That's what they all keep asking me to do...draw a map.
但如果我画错了  他们就会把我钉死在十字架上
And if I mess up, they'll crucify me.
你可以乘热气球环球旅行
You flew around the world in a balloon.
但却怕画不好地图?
And you don't think you can draw up a good map?
飞行...完全是两码事 这是有关于气流的...
Air travel...it's a different animal. It's about wind currents--
你到底知不知道它在哪儿?
Do you or do you not know where it is?
当然  我知道
Yeah, I know where it is.
我就在那儿埋了我的妻子
I went back there to bury my wife.
你为什么那么做?
Why did you do that?
因为那只热气球是我们最有家乡味的东西
Because that balloon was the closest thing we had to home.
你们一直在为了所发生的事
You people have been looking for someone to punish for everything that's happened to you--
找人顶罪  现在你们总算找到了
someone to blame. And now you've got him.
不管我做了什么  我是死定了
Doesn't matter what I do. I'm dead already.
你画好地图  Henry  我会找到你的热气球的
You draw up that map, henry. I'll find your balloon.
但如果你不画...
But if you don't...
你就真的死定了
things are gonna play out just like you said.
嘿  Sun
Hey, sun.
看看我在从林里找到的
Look what I found in the middle of the jungle.
一点都没有化掉  很奇怪  不是么?
It's not even melted or nothing. Crazy, huh?
要分一小块么?
You want to split it?
不了  不了  谢谢
no, no, thanks
我正要去海滩那儿
I was just heading to the beach.
好的  恩  再见  伙计
Okay. Well, later, dude.
你们好  Kwan先生  Kwan太太
你好
对不起让你们久等了
你爸爸最近好吗?
他很好  谢谢关心
帮我问候一下他吧
当然  也再次谢谢你
医生  有结果了么?
恐怕...是个坏消息
超声波显示子宫内膜异位  疤痕组织堵塞了输卵管
也就是说...
就算做了手术  怀孕也是不可能的
你能治好么?  你肯定可以做点什么
我无能为力  很抱歉
我们结婚之前你知道这个吗?
什么?
你一定有企图
我为什么要对你隐瞒?
噢  是啊  我要诱拐一个渔民的儿子
我要出来了
I need out.
他和我说的同和你们说的一样
He told me the same story he told you.
你相信他?
You believe him?
我还不知道  我需要再和他呆段时间
I don't know yet.I need more time with him.
随时都可以
He's all yours.
就明天  我给他点时间考虑
Tomorrow. I want to give him some time to think.
你同意吧?
That's okay with you?
我没和任何人说起过  Ana
I didn't tell anyone, Ana.
这你不用担心
No worries, man.
大得可以放下一张餐桌了  不是么?
Bit large for a dining room table, isn't it?
我们把他截成两半就行了
We cut them in two, it will suit the purpose.
Sayid
Sayid  能和你谈谈么?
Sayid, can I talk to you?
当然
Of course.
单独谈谈
Alone.
不管你要说什么  你可以在这儿说
Whatever you need to say, you can say it here.
是和舱子有关的
It's about the hatch.
噢  你是指那个被锁在储藏室里的人么?
Oh, you mean the guy locked in the closet there?
他怎么了?
What about him?
是去他热气球那儿的
It's to his balloon.
你怎么做到的?
How did you get him to do this?
我用软的
I asked nicely.
Jack和Locke知道这张图么?
Do Jack and Locke know about this?
Jack和Locke正忙于互相担心
Jack  and Locke are a little too busy worrying about Locke and Jack.
我想知道这家伙是不是在说真的
All I want to know is if this guy's telling the truth.
为什么来找我?
Why come to me?
从他脸上的伤痕来看  你对这个也有兴趣
Judging from what you did to his face, that's what you want, too.
去那儿至少要走一天
This is at least a day's walk.
那我们就马上动身
Then we should get going.
你没事吧?
You okay?
没事  谢谢
Fine. Thank you.
那儿的岩壁就是这个了
That cliff there appears to be this.
到这儿为止Henry还是老实的
Score one for Henry.
仅仅标明一个地理标志
Pointing out a geographical touchstone
不代表他会把我们引向他的热气球
does not mean he's leading us to a balloon.
也许不会  但至少我们没有走错岛
Maybe not, but at least we're on the right island.
幽默感不适合他
Humor's not his strong suit.
这句话是对你说的
And I'm saying this to you.
你在看我的屁股?
You looking at my bum?
不是  我在看你的枪
No, I'm looking at your gun.
我的什么?
My what?
也许你该把枪给会用的人
Maybe you should give the gun to somebody who knows how to use it.
我会的  我记得你上次持枪时 有人被你谋杀了
Maybe I will. As I recall, the last time you had a gun, you murdered someone.
够了
That's enough.
我们要走到岩壁脚下  在那儿露营
We'll go as far as the base of the cliff, and we'll camp there.
大概要多久?
How long is it supposed to take?
要两分钟
Uh, up to two minutes.
-我很抱歉  我只是...  -我知道
-I'm sorry. I'm just...  -I know.
Sawyer是从哪儿找到这个的?
Where did sawyer find one of these, anyway?
我是说  谁会带着测孕棒坐飞机  对么?
I mean, who flies with a pregnancy test, right?
你有用过么?
Have you ever taken one?
恩
Yeah.
谢谢你陪着我...
Thank you for waiting with me...
并且没有问为什么是你而不是Jin陪我
不客气
You're welcome.
时间到了
It's time.
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
是百分百正确么?
Is it 100% sure?
只有一个人能回答
There's only one way to find out.
这些测孕棒是很精确的
These tests are pretty accurate.
你知道  可能在第一周会出现错误的阴性
You know, false negative in the first week maybe,
但阳性就是阳性
but a positive is a positive.
但那是不可能的
But it's impossible.
噢  不  这是可能的
Oh, no. It's possible.
你感到走路不稳?  头很轻?
You feeling queasy? Light-headed?
拜托  Jack  这是私事   不要告诉任何人
Please, Jack. This is private. Nobody can know.
你不准备告诉Jin?
You're not gonna tell Jin?
合适时我会的  只是...
In time, I will. It's just...
这很复杂
it's complicated.
就像Jin是这个岛上最后一个知道 你会说英语的人?
As complicated as Jin being the last one on the island to find out you spoke english?
Sun  我建议...只是个建议 因为我是最后一个这么说的
Sun, my advice...and it's just that, because I'm the last person to ask about this,
你应该告诉他
but you should tell him.
而且你得把你所有的事都告诉他...所有真相
And when you do, you should tell him everything...the whole truth.
我得回去舱里了
I'm gonna get back to the hatch.
恭喜你  Sun
Congratulations, Sun.
你经常去那儿  Jack  没什么事吧?
You've been down there a lot, Jack. Is everything okay?
当然  一切都好
Sure. Yeah. Everything's fine.
你没事吧?
You okay?
Sun?
Sun  你没事吧?
Sun, are you all right?
恩  没事
Yes, I'm fine.
你整节课都心烦意乱
You were distracted for our entire lesson.
一定有什么事
You're not fine.
我们...Jin和我去看了医生
We...Jin and I went to see a doctor.
他说我不能生孩子
He said I cannot have children.
我...很遗憾  Sun
I'm... very sorry, Sun.
我却很高兴
I was glad.
为什么我们会在这儿?
因为你教我英文
事实上你一个月前就可以说得很流利了
你为什么学英文?
因为...
我想移居去美国
你打算离开Jin
我曾为了一个女人而去美国
因为我知道我爱上她了
但你却不能脱离你的生活
Jin呢?  他是我生活的一部分么?
我该留下就因为...
我没说你应该为了Jin而留下
I'm not saying you should stay for jin.
介意我坐下么?
You mind?
你能睡时应该多睡会儿
You should sleep while you can
嗯...我睡不着
Yeah...I can't sleep.
大家都不喜欢我
People don't like me.
我平生试了所有的可能
I've tried to get them to most of my life.
我想我得暂时放弃这个念头
I guess I just gave up awhile back.
我是说...我就是我
I mean...I am what I am.
但是你...你恨我是有理由的
But you...you've got a good reason to hate me.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我为我所做的道歉
I'm sorry for what I did.
你在保护你们的人
You were trying to protect your people.
杀死Shannon的不是你  而是他们
It wasn't you that killed Shannon. It was them.
一旦我知道他是他们的一员...
And once we find out he is one of them...
我是不会留情的
then something will have to be done.
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
要下雨了
It's gonna rain.
我们得出发了
We should get moving.
早上好  谁要吃早饭?
Morning! Who wants breakfast?
我有番木瓜果
I have papayas and papayas.
我们走吧
Let's go.
对啊  干吗要吃呢?
Right. Why eat?
就是这儿了
This is it.
他的热气球应该很大  是么?
His balloon would be rather large, right?
早就知道没有了
Why am I not surprised?
我们得再找找
We need to look some more.
他说热气球就在这儿的
This is where he said it would be.
如果我们要回头  Sayid
If I'm gonna back your play on this, Sayid,
我们得确信这里没有
we need to be sure.
我把这地方分成三块
I'll divide the area into three grids.
我们彻头彻尾得找
We'll search as thoroughly as you please.
哦  天哪
Oh, for the love of god!
哦  不 不 不 不  这不是用来抓鱼的
Oh, no, no, no, no. It's not for fish.
不 不 不  是抓牡蛎的
No, no, no. Oysters.
牡蛎
Pearl.
珍珠  给Rose的珍珠
Oyster. Pearl. For rose.
没有牡蛎  这儿没有牡蛎
No oyster here.Ah. Of course not.
当然了  这儿怎么会有?
Why would there be?
哟  伙计们
Sawyer
你还这么忙啊
Way to go, papa-san. You didn't waste much time.
我应该给你根雪茄庆祝  可惜我给抽完了
I'd give you a cigar, Bernie, but I'm fresh out.
Sun怀孕了?
Sun's pregnant?
别大声  伙计  我想Jin还不知道呢
Keep it down there, Suzy. I don't think Jin Sr. here knows yet.
你在干什么?
我在弥补我的错误
你不需要这样做...
不  我要
-我需要你  -什么?
我不想再吵架了  而且我不能...
我不能和其他人交流
我听不懂他们说的
我需要你  Sun
-Jin  我...  -都过去了  我很抱歉
-我错了...  -我怀孕了
什么?  你...
我怀孕了  Jin
Jin  你听我说
什么?
有些事...有些事我要告诉你
Sun  Sun
Kim医生?
可以上车么?
什么事啊?
拜托  我有话和你说
等等  等下  Sun
我犯了个严重的错误
不能生孩子的不是你
什么?
是他  是你的丈夫不能生育
可是你为什么...
我不得已  我很抱歉  你的丈夫...
他是给你父亲办事的
如果我和他说他不能生育
他会把我家移平的
那你为什么现在来告诉我?
因为你该知道真相
你为什么不早跟我说?
我怎么能说?
如果是我...是我不能... 怎么会有孩子?
我向你发誓  Jin
我没和其它男人好过
这是真的
那这就是个奇迹了
如果是个男孩...
我想用我父亲的名字中的一个字来给他取名
也可以考虑一下我妈妈的
我们要不要告诉其他人?
Jack和Kate已经知道了
Sawyer可能也知道了...
那Benard一定也知道了
我们很幸运不用一个个去说了
准备好去吃午饭了么?
我们回去吧
我还想再呆一会儿
独自一个人
如果你同意的话
好吧
我在海滩等你
我爱你
我...爱...你
I...love...you.
那本书怎样?
How is it?
人们拒绝先知  杀了他们
Men reject their prophets and slay them.
但是他们又热爱他们的殉教者 尊敬被他们杀了的人
But they love their martyrs and honor thosewhom they have slain.
那么殉教者和先知有区别么?
So what's the difference between a martyr and a prophet?
不管是哪个  最后都得死
Either way, sounds like you end up dead.
就是这样
That's the spirit.
要吃早饭么?
You in the mood for some breakfast?
这电脑是干什么的?
What's the computer for?
没什么
Nothing.
麦片?
Cereal?
你们从哪儿来的麦片?
Wow, where did you guys get cereal?
一直都是这下面的  食品室里都是吃的
It was down here all along. The pantry's full of food.
没过期吧?
How old is it?
你们也没知道多少?
You guys don't know much, huh?
我是说我一直在问这里的各种各样的问题
I mean, I'd be asking all kinds of questions about all this stuff down here.
你们看起来并不是这么好奇
You guys don't even seem that curious.
麦片你还要不要吃了?
Do you want the cereal or don't you?
这肯定是对我表现好的奖励
This must be my reward for good behavior, huh?
我想我给Ana画了地图后 终于得到你们一点好意了
I guess I earned myself some goodwill for finally drawing that map for Ana.
什么地图?
What map?
去我热气球那儿的地图
To my balloon.
-你知...  -不
-Did you...  -No.
你们互相还真是不信任啊
Wow. You guys have some real trust issues, don't you?
难怪她都不告诉你们
Guess it makes sense she didn't tell you.
我是说  你们一直在相互较劲...
I mean, with the two of you fighting all the time...
如果我是他们中的一个...
'course if I was one of them...
那些你们认为是敌人的人...
these people that you seem to think are your enemies...
我会怎么做?
what would I do?
那就不会有什么热气球了
Hmm. There'd be no balloon.
我会画一张去隐秘的地方的地图
So I'd draw a map to a real secluded place
像是山洞或是草丛什么的 设圈套的好地方...
like a cave or some underbrush...
设下埋伏
good place for a trap.
当你们的朋友去到那儿时
An ambush.
一群我的人会等在那里
And when your friends got there, a bunch of my people would be waiting for 'em.
然后他们会拿你们的朋友来和我交换
And then they'd use them to trade for me.
还好我不是他们的一员
I guess it's a good thing I'm not one of them, huh?
你们有牛奶么?
You guys got any milk?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====